This is...
A time machine.
I'm from the year 2036.
Suzuha...
I'm the time traveler...
John Titor.
Even the billions of heartbeats in the world
suujuuoku mo no kodou no kazu sae
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
are nothing to you but insignificant
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
Whether we’re trapped in the past or lamenting over the future
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
predetermination does not allow even the slightest mistake
mugen ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
The infinite dreams and futures before us
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no genri
are but vain privileges allowed to us
yuugen sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
Finitude is what both clock hands show
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
toward a cruel destiny and choice
Hacking to the Gate
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
So now I cross worldlines every second
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
because I want to protect that smile of yours
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no loop e to
And so, a time loop without sadness will once again
nomikomareteyuku kodoku no kansokusha
engulf me, the lone observer
Missing Link
Necrosis
In the year 2036,
the world is ruled by SERN.
It's an oppressive, totalitarian society— a dystopia.
People were robbed of their freedom,
and they live like zombies.
Anyone who disobeyed was killed.
I was part of the resistance,
fighting to free the world from SERN's control.
To change this forsaken world...
...I entered the time machine my father left me.
It was all to change the future.
Then everything you wrote on @channel...
Yes, most of it was true.
But SERN is a research organization,
not a ruling body.
On the net, I told John Titor that many times.
Wait!
Does that mean you
are KuriGohan and Kamehameha?
Titor identified himself,
so it wouldn't be fair if I didn't, right?
Then I'll identify myself as well.
I was using the name Hououin Kyouma—
We know that.
SERN succeeded in developing a time machine.
Since they were the only ones able to
interfere with the fourth dimension, time,
they remade the world map, so to speak,
and Makise Kurisu is the one
who contributed the most to the time machine's development.
She's hailed as the mother of the time machine.
I worked with SERN?
No way!
Why would I work with people who
perform human experiments?
That's what happened in the future.
So that's why you disliked me...
What about the future me?
Okabe Rintaro is a famous terrorist.
Terrorist?
A terrorist who fought SERN.
And you're both...
...dead in the year 2036.
I need to hurry.
Wait.
You're going to say something crazy like that,
then just return to the future?
That's why I'm leaving.
I'm going to the past to change the future.
To 1975...
1975?
SERN succeeded in developing a time machine
due to the one created in Akihabara in 2010.
You mean the PhoneWave?
SERN used a communication monitoring system
to gather all the information they could on time machines from around the world.
I think the first D-Mail you sent tripped the system.
The message I sent in front of Radio Kaikan?
Yes.
So if we delete the message from SERN's database,
the future will change.
We can go to the Beta worldline, where SERN
never successfully created a time machine.
Will that save Mayuri?
Probably.
Then we should start hacking SERN's database immediately...
We need the IBN 5100 for that.
I see. So that's why...
My task was to go to 1975,
find an IBN 5100,
and get it to Okabe Rintaro,
but I stayed too long to look for my father.
I should've left earlier.
Is everything okay?
It's...
It's broken.
This is bad!
What do we do?
I'll think of something.
You hide.
Run when you can.
Anyone here?
Who's there?
Stay back!
I'm in the middle of an operation
to end the Organization's schemes!
This is a level 17 top secret mission,
so stay away from this place!
This way! Hurry!
Hey!
Wait!
We're running.
Hurry!
I don't know what happens in the future,
but right now, I'm a lab mem just like you!
Okabe!
You're safe?
Let's go!
What do we do?
We can't go back there.
Was the time machine broken?
Was it from when it crashed into the roof?
It didn't crash.
There was an error in calculating the coordinates,
so it appeared there.
When I arrived, it wasn't broken.
Then when?
If I had to guess, I'd say that thunderstorm we had...
It might've been hit by lightning or flooded...
It's my fault...
...because I stopped you then...
I'll use the time leap machine...
We can only use it to go back 48 hours.
We can't get back to that night.
Okarin!
And Kurisu and Suzu are with you!
You didn't go home?
Mayushii said we should have a party to celebrate
the time machine's completion after all.
Daru and I went shopping!
I said we were done for the day!
I'm sorry, Mayuri.
We have to talk about something important.
Okarin?
Just go home for today.
We'll have the party another time.
All right,
but don't do anything dangerous.
Mayushii is worried.
It'll be fine.
I promise.
See you tomorrow then!
Yeah.
I heard the trains stopped.
Seriously?
We'll have to repair the time machine.
First, go back to five hours ago,
when the time leap machine was completed.
From there, go back 48 hours
to 2:00 PM on the 11th.
That's the most time we have.
I'll finish the time machine during those two days,
no matter what.
If I can't, I'll redo those two days as many times as it takes.
This isn't to save the world.
It's a mission to save Mayuri.
Okabe?
What's wrong?
Gather all the lab mems right away.
There's something I want to talk to them about.
Future tech is great.
This must be photoshopped.
Can you fix it?
Miss Amane, you can't do it yourself?
I really can’t.
My father's the one who made it.
There's no way we can fix a time machine
from 2036 using today's technology.
We won't know until we try.
Anyway, try to do it in two days, Daru.
You're our only hope.
Why two days?
Well...
Just do it!
If you can, I'll do anything you want.
Teacher, I want to have a day long date with Faris!
All right. I'll make it happen somehow.
No, that's impossible.
I can do anything!
Believe in me.
You're serious? For real?
I promise,
so do it.
Very well!
One more thing, okay?
If I fix it, in addition to the IBN 5100,
get me a cel from the legendary
1975 magical girl anime, Ragical Girl Omit!
Get to work.
Should I help too?
No, you need to finish the time leap machine.
We should get back to the lab.
Hey, aren't you all forgetting something?
We should look for Suzu's dad.
I'm all right...
No, you're not!
You got in the time machine
because you had a job to do,
but you also wanted to see your dad, right?
So Mayushii wants to help you find him.
Your dad's name was Barrel Titor, right?
That was his code name.
I don't know his real name.
Where's "Amane" from?
From my mother.
My only clue is this little badge he had.
Your dad is in 2010's Akihabara, right?
Okay, Mayushii will be the investigator.
Shiina Mayuri... is a good girl, isn't she?
Think you can fix it?
I can't say for sure,
but looking at it, I guess...
it's kind of like the PhoneWave.
Then there's a chance you'll be able to fix it, right?
I wonder if your dad's nearby.
He knew that we were in Akiba in 2010, right?
I think so,
but I never heard from him directly.
I've never met him.
Everything was in his will.
My dad was researching a time machine separately from SERN...
to change the future.
I'm here to carry on his legacy.
I really am sorry...
but if I can fix the time machine, it's possible that
we'll find your dad before you get back from 1975.
So keep this a secret from Okarin
and try to get me that cel...
That's a pretty straightforward way to do it.
We're supposed to be the Future Gadget Laboratory,
yet you don't have a more futuristic way?
Nothing's as convenient.
Future Gadget #2, alt. edition,
version 2.67.
AKA the Bamboo Copter Camera.
There's a CCD camera on the lower body.
Surprisingly practical.
Could we use this for an aerial search?
The camera spins too,
so the video you receive revolves at a high speed.
You're at version 2.67, and that still isn't fixed?
That's the first one we’ve made.
Daru came up with the name, along with the version.
There's no real meaning.
Where's Daru?
He's still hard at work.
The divergence meter...
You made it, so I think you should have it.
If this number goes above 1%, the future will change.
With your Reading Steiner,
you're the only one who will know.
Did I give you that before I died in the future?
No, I never met you.
You were a founding member of the resistance I was in.
I founded the resistance?
How stupid.
I couldn't even save Mayuri,
and I kept on living
like a stupid little kid in a fantasy world?
It wasn't stupid!
It was an honest, brave desire to save the world!
Hey, mister...
I am mad scientist!
It's so cool!
Sonuvabitch.
Yes, what is it?
So you speak Japanese, huh?
There's something I want to ask you.
Ever seen this before?
I want to know where it came from.
Can you look into it for me?
The remember.
Sorry, it's difficult.
Are you sure he speaks Japanese?
If you remember, contact me here.
Maybe this’ll be created in the near future,
but it doesn't exist now?
Maybe it's fate that I never meet my dad, after all.
Want to give up on it?
You're giving up?
We still have a day!
What are you—
I want to prioritize saving Mayuri!
Even so, you're a lab mem and a friend.
I want to help you if I can!
So why are you already giving up?
D-Don't yell at me, okay?
I'm sorry.
Please!
What is she...
There was a kidnapping yesterday!
I'm looking for the criminal. He wore a badge like this!
Please help us!
Oh, Okarin!
Look! Look!
Mayuri...
Good idea, right?
It was Mayushii's idea!
I think everyone might go, "Huh?" when they see this.
This is
Operation Big Victory with Mayushii's Pamphlets!
A kidnapping is pushing it, don't you think?
What if the police start looking for us?
Oh, no! Run!
What?
Hey, you guys!
Wait!
I'm sorry.
From now on, ask me about these operations first.
That includes the name.
What are you doing?
Oh, it's Christina.
Good timing.
I heard something pretty serious.
What?
When I went to buy lunch, I overheard the clerks.
Amane's dad might be a kidnapper.
Wh-What?
What's going on?
How's it going?
Something to drink.
If you were awesome, you would've brought me
an ice-cold zero-calorie cola.
Well?
Can we fix the time machine?
Probably by tomorrow.
You worked this whole time, but that's still amazing!
Daru's the real deal.
Even if he looks unhealthy and kind of dim.
Don't judge him by his looks.
Yeah, I've changed my mind about him.
Then you can help me too.
Then, in the steaming-hot confines of the time machine,
we can forget our shame and take off our clothes...
Shut up, pervert!
Daru and Suzu look good together.
Together? How?
I don't really know how to say it...
They just do.
What's up?
Don't worry about it!
Mayuri was just saying something weird.
But if the time machine gets fixed,
I'm worried about Suzu when she rides it!
If it could fit two people, I could go with you...
Why would you go with her?
Why else?
I'd hold Suzu's hand really tight, and I'd say,
"It's okay! Mayushii's with you, so it's okay!"
Hey, I'm saying this because
I don't think I'll ever have the chance to say it again.
What? That's an exaggeration.
I'm really grateful to you all.
When I first came here, I didn't know anyone.
Even though this era is much more peaceful,
somehow, to me, it was really scary...
but now I have lots of friends.
I'm really happy that I could come here,
and that I could spend time with you guys.
I'm glad I had the chance to be a lab mem, if only for a little while.
I'm glad I had the chance to spend time with you...
Suzuha...
Okabe Rintaro!
Change the future.
Make it a free world, like this one!
Suzuha?
Yes?
Hello?
Mad scientist so cool?
The guy from this morning?
I remembered...
About that pin badge from yesterday...
You found her father?
I'll be right there!
Wait!
kisei sareta shikai mujihi naru
With my field of view restricted
juuni no shihai nogarerarenai
I cannot escape the merciless control of the twelve
ansoku no asu wo negatta
While wishing for a tomorrow of repose
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
I headed for the sacred event horizon in my hand
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
Pledges are imprisoned, and false evidences are showing their outline
seimei no tenchi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
This world of life blindly lets the time pass by
habatake butterfly
Spread your wings
kiseki no butterfly
butterfly of miracles
anata he sasagu
I dedicate it to you
namida no butterfly
Oh butterfly of tears
mabushii butterfly
butterfly of radiance
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
everything will now be rewritten